The Big Sky I Wanted to See
I've wanted to be an idol since I was a little girl.
But I've never tried to make it happen.
I've been running away from it because I was afraid.
But I found you and you fell in love with me
Because of you, the fans who found me and loved me
Even when I'm scared and feel like running away
I'm able to look forward and do my best
In the past year
I've met 22 members here
I have met here
have become very important to me.
It's been a very short and intense year.
but it wasn't all fun and games.
But it wasn't only about the fun, it was also about the support
I was able to gain confidence.
There were times when I wanted to run away from this place
But now that I have met you all
I'm glad to have met you all.
This is the place where I belong
You made it for me
Looking back on the past year
I'm really glad that I joined Oni.
I'm so glad that I could meet you and the members like this.
is one of the greatest things in my life.
I feel that every day was like my youth, and
I want to be the kind of person who can bring smiles to many people
I want to become a person who can bring smiles to many people
I want to be the kind of person who can bring smiles to many people's faces.
I've learned a lot about the warmth of people.
I also think that it is not so easy to be young.
As I grow older, I become afraid of having hopes and dreams.
But if there are people who think they are really bad people
I want to tell them that you are not a bad person.
The name of our group, "Blue Sky I Wish I Could See" is also in the name of our group.
The name of our group, "Blue Sky I Wanted to See," is also filled with hope that we ended up with a beautiful blue sky after chasing our dreams.
It is a group name filled with hope.
It's a group name filled with hope. From now on, the 23 of us will continue to work together
We will be a group that can be a shining hope for everyone.
Thank you for watching!
It was at this time that I met Sakamichi Gurfs, and they gave me hope and courage.
You gave me hope and courage.
I hope I can be that kind of person this time.
My name is Hayasaki Suzuki.
Now that I've come this far, I want to be an idol.
I want to do everything I can.
I don't want to have any regrets.
I'm Hitomi Hasegawa.
I will be performing my original dance choreography.
I applied without hesitation.
I believe my perseverance is second to none.
I am pleased to announce the winners of the competition!
Ms. Karen Yanagibori
Ms. Suzuki Hayasaki
Aya Nishimori
I can't wait to tell my family!
I feel like I'm fluffy!
I can't wait to tell my family.
I can't wait to tell my family!
Good morning!
Please try to absorb as much as you can and bring it back home with you!
I look forward to working with you.
My name is Cocona Yoshimoto.
I'm able to talk about many things I've never talked about before.
I hope we can get to know each other better.
I'm so frustrated that I'm the only one who can't do it.
I was so frustrated that I started to cry.
But all the members gave me a lot of advice.
That's how I feel.
Yes, you see...
That's great.
Today, I'd like to talk about something important.
In the first scene, we're all going to be selected.
Everyone will sing.
I'm thinking of having the goat sing the center.
You're quitting.
But he's looking good.
It's amazing
He said we should do our best as a group of 23.
That was really encouraging.
And I thought to myself, "I'm going to do my best to reach the audience with these 23 people.
I thought again that we should do our best to reach the people who are watching us.
I want to be a group that is loved by each and every one of you.
You're so good!
It's not about being made to do something.
I want to be loved by each and every one of you.
They take pride in their work and do their best when they have to.
I want to catch up with everyone and do my best.
That really got me fired up.
I don't know...
I just...
I wanted to get out in front a little more.
So...
I'll do my best
I will do my best
From now on, as a global lamprey
As a global lamplighter, I'd like to be a rival.
This is a little bit really tough and difficult
I was selected out of 35,678 members
How have you changed as a future member of this group?
I want to change for the better.
My name is Yuho Aoki, I'm 20 years old and I'm from Okinawa, Japan.
I want to grow and do my best from now on!
I'm Ai, from Tokyo, Okinawa.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
I often have to reshoot when I do something like this, so I was a little nervous and worried that I wouldn't make a mistake.
I was nervous and worried that I might make a mistake.
But in the end, we were able to have fun shooting.
I'm really glad that we were able to do it.
I had never seen a camera before.
I really felt that this was how they were taking pictures.
It was an excellent experience and a lot of fun.
But I was really nervous.
I think it went well.
Thank you very much.
All together
Seino
Room Search Rejou
It was the first time I saw a large studio and it was hard to get a good personality too
Bye bye!
We decided on a leader.
So, I announced today,
Then please give me a leader reach.
I think we're a little far from it.
I hope everyone in this group
I hope everyone can have fun in this group.
I hope I can make you laugh and be there for you when you are having a hard time.
I hope I can make you laugh and be there for you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Please take care of me.
Chorus
When I heard that we were going through, I was really surprised.
It was difficult at first
But as we did the test, I was able to get the notes better and better.
I don't really know what it feels like to be on stage.
Hello everyone!
This is the blue sky I've always wanted to see.
Today, August 30th, we celebrated our debut day!
So please listen to this.
This is the blue sky I wanted to see.
Thinking about the blue sky
I still remember the days when
I waved my hands wide in the sunlight
With my short-sleeved shirt still on
The event is open to those who have purchased the debut single released in the third grade and have won the lottery.
The number of people who will be coming to the event is about 100.
Of course, it's a lot smaller than we expected, but we want you to be very aware of that.
But I want you to be very conscious of the fact that you're going to make these 100 people happy and give them back to us.
Yes, sir.
If you can't make these 100 people happy, you'll never get 100, 1,000, or 10,000 customers.
Please concentrate on that today.
I can see from the stage that you're feeling pretty passable.
Let's do it.
Music
music
I knew we didn't have a full house.
But when we started rehearsing
I realized that our ability is not yet this good
I've been thinking about it a little bit.
There are parts that are frustrating
I'm trying my best!
I'm doing my best! I'm doing my best!
I love, love 23 years!
I'm looking forward to your continued support!
I sometimes wonder if I couldn't see the whole venue because I was in the center.
I'm doing my best, and the fans who tell me I'm doing my best...
I think everyone realizes that now.
I also feel really frustrated, but I'm not going to stop thanking you.
I hope I can do my best from now on.
Thank you very much.
Next year on January 31, the second single of "Blue Sky I Wanted to See" will be released.
For the second single, we would like to adopt a selection system.
We have also decided on the name of the selected members.
We will call it "Aozora Gumi".
The members who didn't make it into the Aozora group, we will name them as well.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
This team will be called Spider Team.
Now, I would like to announce the members of the Aozora group.
Aoi Anno
Yuzu Ito
Ami Kanazawa
Hiko Ito
I have a feeling of frustration.
but I am not yet at the level to be selected.
I'm also frustrated that I'm able to accept it.
I feel frustrated
I feel bad.
I've only said I'm frustrated since I went here.
Have you been sad? In my life.
That's what I'm trying to remember over there on the edge.
I'll try to sing it.
If I can get that look, I can write it.
If not...
I'm gonna keep going until it comes out.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll stick with it. I'll stick with it.
I'll stick with you. I'll stick with you until it comes out.
So that I can understand how he's feeling.
It's a little hard to put emotion into this.
Let's give it a try.
Maybe sing with a little more passion.
Okay.
Cut.
The expression I want is a sad face.
Look at the camera.
This is the way you look at someone who didn't get your feelings.
Yes, cut.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Yes, yes...
Cut.
Cut! I didn't mean to be rude.
Cut! I didn't mean no disrespect.
I can see more of the code.
But it's moving from the heart.
I think you have to put more and more into it to get it across.
Try it again.
But I'm not saying, "This is great." I'm saying, "This is great.
I'm not saying, "This is fine." I'm saying, "You know what?
And when I couldn't get it out...
And when I couldn't get it out, he would tell me to put more.
I learned a lot from you.
Thank you very much.
I guess I was feeling more pressure than I thought.
I don't know...
The second round...
It's a very selective game.
Why do you think
why do you think you were chosen?
and I had no idea.
I had no idea.
I had to do well for that.
I've been trying not to think about it.
I tried not to think about it.
I was first.
I wasn't in the front.
So, if you ask me if I did well
I'm not sure if I did it well or if I got a good response.
I don't really know.
I'm sorry.
It was a mess.
It's just...
My lacrimal gland
collapsed.
Thank you for your letter.
Thank you very much.
From Osaka.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Yes, ma'am.
I remember you.
You have a great smile!
I'm glad I've seen you since the review.
I was looking forward to it so much I couldn't sleep.
I haven't had a day like that since elementary school field trips.
So I thought you must be really enjoying yourself.
That's great!
It's my first time performing live, so I hope it's a success.
I hope the audience will be happy to have come to the show.
I hope we can give a live performance that will make the people who come feel happy to have come.
What are your dreams for the future?
I'm going to do my best!
A.A.O.!
LOL!
It's so nice!
The blue penlights!
The blue penlights were awesome!
The space shop is great!
Space is nice.
I like it better when you want to do it.
I can see your back.
I see you.
I'm... I'm...
I'm moved. Well, it's been a while since I've cried.
You know.
I've been watching it on TV for a long time, and now I can see it right in front of my eyes.
I was really moved.
Check it out!
It's a parachute!
You're gonna love it.
Let's move on.
I can't wait for it to be over.
I'm having so much fun.
It made me feel like I have to work harder.
It made me feel positive.
I'm so happy to see so many fans coming to the show.
I'm very happy, but
but even if you are not a fan...
Even if you're not a fan...
I'm sure there are artists who want to go to live shows even if you're not a fan of theirs.
I hope I can make it that kind of concert.
I want to make it so that people will say, "Bokuoku no seigai is really good.
I want to be the kind of person who says "Boku Sei's live is really good
I want to be like that.
Thank you for watching!
We had always said that we wanted to do a live concert together.
I was so happy that we could do it like this.
I'm not going to make the venue bigger, but...
I hope that more and more people will support me
I hope to see more and more scenery one day.
I hope to see more and more scenery with everyone in the audience.
I also want more and more people to listen to my single.
I have many goals.
Thank you very much for coming to Bodding Zero.
Thank you very much.
I'm Karen Omoshiroi.
I'm Nisshin Tsukihiho.
I am a shell.
I will try my best to break out of my shell and try more things!
Compassion.
This year, I'm going to build up my self-confidence.
I will put myself out there.
A step forward.
More regret.
Gratitude.
Guts.
Offsabor.
Hey, that's a rock-paper-scissors!
Progress.
Thank you for your hard work.
Luck is the point of contention.
out of the clouds, blue skies are spreading
It means that we can overcome difficulties with our efforts
After that, a bright future awaits you.
Mogumi's solo show will be held
5, 6, 7, 8
Recently, it has been easy for everyone to express their opinions during the lessons.
I feel that everyone is becoming more positive.
I think it's not only individual issues, but also the group as a whole.
We all found our goals and challenges as a group.
We will continue to set and achieve these goals little by little.
Enjoy the lesson!
Everyone's skills have improved.
We are now able to communicate with each other, and
I think we've become closer to each other.
Who's there?
I'll always remember you.
Until the graduation of the second single
Hit project live streaming!
Let's make it together!
10,000 teruteru versions!
It will look like this
Completed
There are 3193 sheep!
Don't miss this opportunity!
Please pass this way!
It's been about 3 months since our first one-man show, and we've done a lot of different things, and I think we've grown in some areas and in others we still have a long way to go,
But we will do our best today to give what we can to the audience and to make it to the next stage.
Let's do our best for another day.
It's a really cool song.
I hope everyone in the audience will get goosebumps while listening to this song.
Eight colors.
I'm sure there are people who like this song a lot.
I like it too, so I want to treasure it.
Music
But I'm hoping to show you a new Coconar
I hope I can show you something new
I want everyone to be surprised
I want to show that I can do this kind of heart
I hope I can show you that I can do this kind of heart
I'll do my best.
Paint it all over again, everything up to today
The past is a fuzzy color
Your memories will be pitch black.
I want to make myself pure white.
I've been researching how to express myself.
I've been working on it.
It's fun.
I practiced so, so, so hard.
When there was no one in the group, there was no one.
We were all a bit nervous and flustered after about 3 months, but I think we have grown a lot since then.
Let's continue to be young together!
The release of the third single has been decided!
Now, let me announce the Aozora group for the third single!
Aoi Anno
Yuzu Ito
And Akita Lian
These 11 members will be the third single Aozora group!
I think I did a great job.
I think I gave 100%.
I think I gave 120%.
But
I'm still not satisfied with the results.
I don't think it's a lack of effort on my part.
I think there is.
Yeah.
I just have to keep trying.
I'm so disappointed.
You gave me so much support.
I feel like I didn't live up to that.
I'm overwhelmed with emotion.
This was our first music video shoot since we joined the Aozora group.
At first, I was worried that I would be left behind.
I was really anxious.
But I didn't know if I should tell the members about my anxiety or not.
I was conflicted about whether or not I should express my anxiety to the members.
But I thought it might be a good idea to tell them.
There was a time when I suddenly thought
We had a basic practice session.
I couldn't do it at all.
I was wondering what to do, when one of the members approached me and said...
Yes, you did.
Karen called out to me.
That was a great support for me.
I was able to do my best.
But it was a lot of fun.
The most important thing is that we want to become a bigger and bigger group.
I want us to become like a national love group.
I hope we can become like that.
We definitely have to be in a hurry.
I think we should never stop being in a hurry.
No matter how hard things get, we won't leave anyone behind.
I want us to be a group that can move forward together.
I want to be someone who can support the members around me.
When I see them perform live, I would like to see them dance on a bigger stage.
I can't imagine it at all now.
I can't imagine it at all now, but I would like to do it with a bang.
I'd like to do it with a bang.
Well, since today is the first anniversary, let's have fun and show our appreciation to everyone.
Let's have fun and enjoy it.
Well then, I'll pray for you to change your clothes today.
But I feel like I'm going to cry.
You did a great job, really. Thank you, for always working so hard.
I'm so happy that I've been able to go on like this for a whole year with everyone I love.
I'm so happy that we've been able to move forward.
I want to enjoy the past.
I'm going to have fun.
Here we go!
Seino
To the sun at the end of the day, dreams and hopes for the future
Deliver!
The blue sky I've always wanted to see
Thank you for watching!
I am so happy that all 23 of us made it to this day without missing a single person!
I love you fans and I'm always so happy to see you!
It is so much fun to be with you all.
From now on, I will do my best to help this group.
I have a dream that I want to achieve, and I never want to give up on it.
I hope I can make myself like myself more and more.
I hope I can become more like myself.
There are people who say they like me even though I am like this.
I am very much saved by such words.
I am able to celebrate the first anniversary of Blue because of all of you who support me.
I think it's because of all of you who support me.
Because I want to see you all
I can do my best tomorrow.
I am so happy to meet such wonderful friends
I'm very happy.
I love my fans so much, but I can't express it well enough.
I'm still a bit of an idol, but I'm willing to go as far as I can to show you how much I love you.
I'm serious now, so there are many times when I'm at my limits.
Even so, I'm really glad that I joined this group.
I hope to have a lot of youth with you all in the second year.
one of the biggest things in my life.
one of the greatest things in my life.
I feel that every day was like my youth, and
It was like a dream come true for me to be an idol, which I always wanted to be.
There are times when I really want to stop and go, but
I am truly blessed by the people around me.
I'm sure I wouldn't have been able to do it a year ago.
I really feel that I am growing up thanks to everyone.
I want to be the kind of person who gives people the courage and hope to take the first step forward, and I want BOCAO to become that kind of group.
I hope BOCAO will become such a group.
Is there any scenery you would like to see with BOCAO?
We will definitely take you there.
So I'm glad that you believe in us and will continue to follow us.
A year ago, I was here.
I shouted "Thank you".
I shouted...
Thank you!
Let's continue to live our youth together with Wakao!
I can say with confidence that it was the right decision to continue to be an idol.
I always think of you guys right away.
Even in hard times, I thought that I shouldn't run away from the situation, and I have been able to move forward to this point.
I think it is really wonderful to challenge something.
Let's have youth together!
Whenever you have a hard day, remember today.
I hope that you will walk through life with us so that we can look forward together again.
I'm so happy that we are walking on the same path together at this moment and every moment of this live, and I'm looking forward to seeing you all again in the second year.
I look forward to our second year together.
The word "youth" means to live with hopes and dreams.
That's why we're going into our second year. Let's keep going!
The 23 of us will work together to become a group that can be your bright hope.
We have an announcement.
Let's watch the ETR together!
Thanks to you, Blue Sky.
We are going to have a commemorative live concert at Toyosu Pit on August 30, the day of our debut.
Thank you very much.
Toyosu Pit was the place where we had a mini-live event for our first single,
I am very happy to be here.
It was also the place where I realized how good we are now.
We always talked about how it would be great if we could fill the Toyosi pit again someday, so we decided to do something else.
I hope we can make this concert a place where we can show that we can do something else, and that we can do our best.
I would like to end by singing that song one more time.
With you, who reminded me of myself that I had forgotten
I still knew the future we talked about
mer